A Guide to the Papers of Archie G. Richardson 1918-1976
Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
- Printed
  - Awards and Certificates
    - Alpha Phi Alpha Certificates 1960,1976 (Box-folder 30:1)
    - Awards 1942-1968 (Box-folder 30:2)
  - Pamphlets
    - Constitution and By-Laws of Southside Interscholastic Althetic Association (Box-folder 30:3)
    - Eugenics in the Relation to The New Family and the Law on Racial Integrity 1924 (Box-folder 30:4)
  - Book
    - The Developement of Negro Education in Virginia 1831-1970 (Othertype 30)
  - Degrees
    - Lexington Colored and Graded School May 15, 1918 (Box-folder 30:5)
    - The Virginia Normal and Industrial Institute High School Course-O.S. Aug 30 1923 (Box-folder 30:6)
    - The Virginia Normal and Industrial Institute Bachelor of Arts June 10 1927 (Box-folder 30:7)
  - News Clippings
    - News clippings from a number of newspapers from the State of Virginia (Othertype 31)